Leo: Hello.
Server: Good evening, sir, madam.
What can I get you?
Kim: How about a coffee? I’m still cold.
Server: Yes, madam. And you, sir?
Leo: You know, I’m cold, too. I’ll also have a coffee, thanks.
Server: Here you are!
Leo: Well, here’s to our new house!
Kim: Yes!
Server: You’re new around here, aren’t you?
Leo: Yes, that’s right.
Kim: We just rented the big house on Darwin Road.
Server: Which house? The Travers family’s house?
Leo: Yes.
Server: Oh.
Leo: Is something wrong?
Server: Who showed you the house?
Kim: Barbara. The old lady who lived there before.
Server: Ahh. Barbara. Old Mr. Travers’s daughter.
Some people thought that she was the one who did it.
Kim: The one who did what?
What happened?
Server: Didn’t she tell you?
Leo: Tell us what?
Server: About the murder.
Leo & Kim: Murder?!
Server: Yes, Mr. Travers was murdered in that house in 1965…in his bed.
Kim: Oh, how horrible!
Server: The man who killed Mr. Travers was Barbara’s lover.
The family never lived there again.
They tried to sell the house, but nobody wanted to buy it.
Not after a murder.
That’s why that house is always rented.
Barbara never married, of course.
Leo: Kim?
Kim: Yes?
Leo: Are you thinking what I’m thinking?
Kim: Yes – I don’t want to live in a house where somebody was murdered.
Come on. Let’s go.
Server: Hey, hey, your coffee!
You didn’t drink your coffee… Ah, well.